<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="/content/scripts/feed_theme.css" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>ORileyTan's Epic RSS Feed</title>
    <link>https://orileytan.github.io</link>
    <description>Where I post updates and other stuff that is not related to youtube such as update logs bla bla bla. Oh yea epic credits to B!Soft! Using an external RSS reader or IE is highly recommended.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</webMaster>
    <copyright>Don't steal this feed</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>So I tried</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:12:01 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <comments>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</comments>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I attempted to add light smear effects onto roblox, like the ones applied to street lamps on Shutokou Battle 2 (Dreamcast version) and Wangan Midnight R until Wangan Midnight Maximum Tune 3. It was actually successfull! unfortunately it's laggy as fuck.. no dude I am being serious my friend from EU has a very fucking beefy pc that can run roblox on 200+ fps, the effects enabled and it goes down to 60 fps. I fucking know why it lags too but there is as far as I am aware no function avaiable for the camera to return a table of parts visible by the player soooooo, rest in piece.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First post of 2025</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 9 Jan 2025 09:30:33 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <comments>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</comments>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Amazing, I am about 8 days late from the start of the new year, My Main PC still has a blown PSU, haven't gotten a new one because the price for one is considerably large so expect me to post more rarely for awhile, like I even post often in the first place.

I have been visiting the arcade a bit more often at the meantime, Mostly some Wangan Midnight but I have been trying some rhythm games lately. MaiMai buddies and Pump it up XX.
MaiMai uses a card system similar to Wangan Midnight's card system but MaiMai uses Aime cards, BUUUTTTT, Banapass cards (Now bandai namco passport) does work on Aime readers because of an agreement between SEGA and Bandai Namco. Aime cards will work on Banapass and vice versa because both cards use the same service, all.net, Basically the reason why the connected to servers icon on MaiMai, Maxi4~6RR+ and IDAS7AAX~IDA are the same! I think Konami is in it too but I'm not too sure...

Also a bit of a teaser, I've been working on a game with DZ (The funny blueberry dude) and it's funny... That's all I'm gonna say I am totally in a NDA lol.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mariah Carey is breaching containment</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 10:06:56 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <comments>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</comments>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Only a couple more weeks before december 1st, and the hardware stores in my region has begun seeling christmas crap, Mariah Carey's "All I want for Christmas is you" is going to be a nightmare cuz it's played on loop constantly. The defrosting process has begun.......... How the fuck is that song so populat although? lmao
Oh yea my "More Windows XP content because my PC is still dead after 12 days" video blew up randomly, as of writing it currently has 1,300+ views and  88:1 like to dislike ratio. Genuinely thanks, never expected my shitposts that I made cuz my main pc died to blow up quite well. although my March 2007 ROBLOX client video has 14,279 views as of right now.... It's a 19 second long video why are you guys watching it a lot? lol
I plan to buy a new PSU for my main PC so I can actually have it back, although I'll try to keep the editing style of my shitbox xp videos because you guys seem to like it :)

By the way my windows XP machine is a genuine shitbox. It's specs are 512MB of RAM, 128GB IDE HDD, Intel Pentium 4 at 2GHz. It has Windows 7 loaded on it too and it barely runs. Windows XP runs much better but whoops, my system got hacked, I lost my data but I had an anti-virus.

Additional update: My Evercoss A65 randomly decided to turn back on again which, yay. One problem, the battery only lasts 4 minutes and google play services crashes every 1 second..... I'm just going to move it to the injured category... Hey at least Blehh's car has a companion now!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man it's been awhile since I posted here</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 19:58:35 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>https://orileytan.github.io/oofyards</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://orileytan.github.io/oofyards</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <comments>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</comments>
      <category>Website stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[This quite late haloween update to my website is now out if you're seeing this
https://orileytan.github.io/oofyards
Introducing OOFYARDS, a graveyard of electronic and mechanical doohickeys that have been absolutely fucked by time and or stupidity.

The list inside of the graveyard is likely to continue to grow (until I lose interest lol)
See you all on Christmas]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minor style change</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:05:20 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Website stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[A pretty basic website update adding text shadows and some additional content in the homepage.
Also I changed the background image of the RSS feed to a generic one because I never update the css script that handles this part of the website. and the rest of the website no longer uses the 90s installer background.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cp_steel, Site of alien abduction</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 10:51:53 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <comments>mailto:whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</comments>
      <category>TF2 crap</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2024/002.jpg" length="14112" type="image/jpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Today an unidentified MANn has been abducted in front of the BLU spawn room, The footage avaiable from the incident is brief and not much context can be obtained other than cp_steel at the time being overrun by bots. Are the bots now abducting random players to become more bots?]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update to Randomly Generated Maze</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 08:45:27 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.roblox.com/games/5033769623</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Game updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[General changes
Enabled Environment Diffuse
Improved Bloom
Improved Depth of Field
Made the maze more spooky in lighting
Enabled the user to use any movment options
Forced camera mode to use classic

Additions
Added a flashlight
Added XBOX support (And playstation) (May or may not work)

Play now! https://www.roblox.com/games/5033769623]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAPPY 25TH ANNIVERSARY HALF-LIFE</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 09:42:37 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://half-life.com/en/halflife25/</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Half-Life</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/007.jpg" length="32967" type="image/jpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[VALVe updated Half-Life steam after 19 years and it's epic!
They remade the main menu to resemble the one from the WON builds of Half Life
New player models
New Maps
New Sprays
Added the disable texture filtering for OPENGL
Added the resize UI to match screen size (kinda ugly)
Check the entire changelog here and buy HL1, It's very good
https://half-life.com/en/halflife25/]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I've rebuilt the website</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 16:59:32 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Website stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I've decided to rebuild the website because the current way I store files is very messy (Casually placing all files in the root directory) which yea isn't great and why I did it was because I was creating the website on a Pentium 4 512MB PC with Windows 7 installed which ran very very poorly and also damaged monitor and ATI graphics card (The PC is so old it doesn't have on-board graphics apparently). So I re-built the website so that all files are neatly (almost) organized and added a bunch of changes which may make the site less usable on older devices.

This probably will be the last time that this version of the website will be used (Unless I have to rollback due to some random issue with the new site).
The new site (which is basically almost identical to the previous one) will be launching this december with some site downtime so that devices connected to the site may be able to load the newer version of the site properly because the last time I did this my iPad didn't load the new version but loaded the previous version from cache (images didn't load).]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We tortured ROBLOX servers</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 1 Nov 2023 20:47:14 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/004.jpg" length="6147" type="" />
      <description><![CDATA[So we've decided for no reason to in a private server of a modded version of Natural Disasters survival to enable EVERY DISASTER at 50x, It means 50 of all disasters spawned which crashed the server and caused DZ's computer to freak out and then I set it to 32767 which tanked my pc down to 0.6fps and ate 3GB of RAM so uh yea have some free screenshots.
https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/004.jpg
https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/005.jpg
https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/006.jpg]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RO-CLOCK</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 09:41:31 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>https://orileytan.github.io/ROCLOCK/about</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://orileytan.github.io/ROCLOCK/about</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/ROCLOCK/icon.png" length="438" type="image/jpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[I've just released a new ROBLOX studio plugin which is quite useless unless you actually have multiple stuff to do because what the plugin does is tell you the time. That's all it does, and it also rings every quarter hour so uh yea that's cool download it here. https://orileytan.github.io/ROCLOCK/about]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An old ROBLOX revival that you download onto your pc.</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:02:40 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>https://austiblox.net/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://austiblox.net/</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/002.jpg" length="3665" type="image/jpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Yes an old ROBLOX revival that I use, I actually used it for 2 of my videos related to old ROBLOX because with it old ROBLOX multiplayer is less of a hassle and it is genuinely quite nice. I've been trying to get it working and it has not been going well and it seems to be only my pc as other people can connect, well my anti virus won't shut up but I'm very sure I've configured it properly already so uh yes. Have a free screenshot that I took while I was in a game: https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/003.jpg]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TF2 DEMOS!!!</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 14:03:58 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>https://orileytan.github.io/downloads</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://orileytan.github.io/downloads</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/001.jpg" length="11526" type="image/jpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[I've decided to release a couple of demos that I recorded on TF2 which now won't work on the latest version of TF2, You'll have to download a special version of it on steam specifically for the playback of older demos and VALVe please fix the demo feature on CS2 it crashes on load. And I've finally opened the downloads section of my website which will will be kinda like a catalogue of stuff that you can download from me. (Links may or may not become dead after awhile) HAPPY HALOWEEN 2023!!!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello October</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 8 Oct 2023 12:16:28 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Hello october, It is now spooky month and that comes with some seasonal changes, as you can see almost all branding are now halloween related and low color mode...... Anyways the YT banner one will likely only appear once and never again so uh yes go ahead and archive it if you want or something. And I also changed my ROBLOX character to be haloween themed as well. Currently got a TF2 video being made for YT (Contains oktoberfest) and for ROBLOX uhh, Not a lot of the games on the website has updated for Haloween so uh yes. (Also a rare moment that I actually post content onto this RSS feed).]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Stuff</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:57:44 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I've apparently forgot to upload a short sfm that I rendered back at November 11 2022 and I just created another sfm today and apparently you need QuickTime 7 to render as an MP4 file and without it you can only render AVI files, QuickTime 7 is pretty much legacy software but well SFM hasn't been updated since I think 2013 so makes sense, so I had to reinstall QuickTime 7 and here's the link to it if google ever decides to make it dissapear https://support.apple.com/kb/dl837
. Oh yea I'm working on a Roblox Studio plugin that all it does is, tell the time, Well it does say it outloud if you click on it and it chimes every quarter so uh yes, I am not giving it a release date but when it releases check https://orileytan.github.io/downloads and the site probably will go down so I can setup the downloads page. Oh yea new site feature advertising thing, the site now has a cool button you can put on your webpage if you want to to direct people here and if you do thanks!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I just destroyed a highly advanced piece of military equippment with nothing but a crowbar</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 1 Sep 2023 20:19:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <comments>http://youtube.com/TswcuOTeqQE</comments>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I just destroyed a highly advanced piece of military equippment with nothing but a crowbar! How is it possible you may ask? No idea ask Gearbox! On other notes I've already beaten almost all of Half-Life's games just Opposing Force. I may also try to beat mods for Portal and Half-Life. Oh yeah you may have noticed "The Stream" and if you are scared DO NOT. It's just me testing a "mirror" effect and it's quite easy to replicate, Just setup a webcam and set it to obs's virtual camera.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh no a friend got hacked!</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:23:28 +0700</pubDate>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Ok I still don't get how people still do click random exes on the internet. Oh yea the thing (From the spoof url) originates from Honduras so uh yea that's something. So the file I'm talking about is RobloxTool.exe which according to the very engrish added text file is "leaked method that Big game devs use to get big amounts of Robux or Items for free.", There is genuinely no way to get free robux unless it's a promotion or before 2016. Also Big Game's actual tool is Roblox Studio, They make games not handle the entire website and Roblox doesn't use exe files to test stuff they either use their site test sites or the ROBLOX account or some random alt not a random exe they don't even need it in the first place because of the important thing of they have direct access to site data...

Also instead of labling the attached txt file as "README.TXT" they just used "HowToDO.txt".

Possible Question: So what does said exe does?
My Answer: I have no idea!
WAIT NONONONONO DON'T CLICK OFF FIRST! Uh well the exe is spread on discord so it likely steals your Discord Token, ROBLOSECURITY cookie, and credit card details to sell on some random black market for quite a huge sum of money, Yea most do that. Also it uses your discord account to send to your discord friends so DO NOT EVEN TOUCH IT, Unless you know what you're doing then uh your own risk not mine. Also you should maybe check links a bit more closely because for some reason www.example.com.[ INSERT NATIONAL DNS HERE ] is possible. Oh yea you could send an email to Red de Desarrollo Sostenible Honduras about www.roblox.com.hn and hopefully it gets taken down.

Oh yea I'm gonna scan the exe with https://www.virustotal.com/ and see what happensoh no I've lost access to the trojan because Windows 10's setup is litteraly the worst I've ever used so uh yea can't check sorry.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERYTHING TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 09:47:03 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>http://example.com</link>
      <author>johndoe@example.com</author>
      <comments>http://example.com</comments>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <enclosure url="BACKGROUND.BMP" length="308,278" type="image/bmp" />
      <description><![CDATA[This is to test absolutely everything I can do on this thing]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 08:19:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <description><![CDATA[TEST]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>