<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="rss.css" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>ORileyTan's Epic RSS Feed</title>
    <link>https://orileytan.github.io</link>
    <description>Where I post updates and other stuff that is not related to youtube such as update logs bla bla bla. Oh yea epic credits to B!Soft!</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</webMaster>
    <copyright>Don't steal this feed</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>An old ROBLOX revival that you download onto your pc.</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:02:40 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>https://austiblox.net/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://austiblox.net/</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/002.jpg" length="3665" type="image/jpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Yes an old ROBLOX revival that I use, I actually used it for 2 of my videos related to old ROBLOX because with it old ROBLOX multiplayer is less of a hassle and it is genuinely quite nice. I've been trying to get it working and it has not been going well and it seems to be only my pc as other people can connect, well my anti virus won't shut up but I'm very sure I've configured it properly already so uh yes. Have a free screenshot that I took while I was in a game: https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/003.jpg]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TF2 DEMOS!!!</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 14:03:58 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>https://orileytan.github.io/downloads</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://orileytan.github.io/downloads</guid>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <enclosure url="https://orileytan.github.io/blogimg/2023/001.jpg" length="11526" type="image/jpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[I've decided to release a couple of demos that I recorded on TF2 which now won't work on the latest version of TF2, You'll have to download a special version of it on steam specifically for the playback of older demos and VALVe please fix the demo feature on CS2 it crashes on load. And I've finally opened the downloads section of my website which will will be kinda like a catalogue of stuff that you can download from me. (Links may or may not become dead after awhile) HAPPY HALOWEEN 2023!!!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello October</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 8 Oct 2023 12:16:28 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Hello october, It is now spooky month and that comes with some seasonal changes, as you can see almost all branding are now halloween related and low color mode...... Anyways the YT banner one will likely only appear once and never again so uh yes go ahead and archive it if you want or something. And I also changed my ROBLOX character to be haloween themed as well. Currently got a TF2 video being made for YT (Contains oktoberfest) and for ROBLOX uhh, Not a lot of the games on the website has updated for Haloween so uh yes. (Also a rare moment that I actually post content onto this RSS feed).]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Stuff</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:57:44 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I've apparently forgot to upload a short sfm that I rendered back at November 11 2022 and I just created another sfm today and apparently you need QuickTime 7 to render as an MP4 file and without it you can only render AVI files, QuickTime 7 is pretty much legacy software but well SFM hasn't been updated since I think 2013 so makes sense, so I had to reinstall QuickTime 7 and here's the link to it if google ever decides to make it dissapear https://support.apple.com/kb/dl837
. Oh yea I'm working on a Roblox Studio plugin that all it does is, tell the time, Well it does say it outloud if you click on it and it chimes every quarter so uh yes, I am not giving it a release date but when it releases check https://orileytan.github.io/downloads and the site probably will go down so I can setup the downloads page. Oh yea new site feature advertising thing, the site now has a cool button you can put on your webpage if you want to to direct people here and if you do thanks!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I just destroyed a highly advanced piece of military equippment with nothing but a crowbar</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 1 Sep 2023 20:19:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>whatnamesaeravaiablethisthingisannoying@hotmail.com</author>
      <comments>http://youtube.com/TswcuOTeqQE</comments>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I just destroyed a highly advanced piece of military equippment with nothing but a crowbar! How is it possible you may ask? No idea ask Gearbox! On other notes I've already beaten almost all of Half-Life's games just Opposing Force. I may also try to beat mods for Portal and Half-Life. Oh yeah you may have noticed "The Stream" and if you are scared DO NOT. It's just me testing a "mirror" effect and it's quite easy to replicate, Just setup a webcam and set it to obs's virtual camera.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh no a friend got hacked!</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:23:28 +0700</pubDate>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Ok I still don't get how people still do click random exes on the internet. Oh yea the thing (From the spoof url) originates from Honduras so uh yea that's something. So the file I'm talking about is RobloxTool.exe which according to the very engrish added text file is "leaked method that Big game devs use to get big amounts of Robux or Items for free.", There is genuinely no way to get free robux unless it's a promotion or before 2016. Also Big Game's actual tool is Roblox Studio, They make games not handle the entire website and Roblox doesn't use exe files to test stuff they either use their site test sites or the ROBLOX account or some random alt not a random exe they don't even need it in the first place because of the important thing of they have direct access to site data...

Also instead of labling the attached txt file as "README.TXT" they just used "HowToDO.txt".

Possible Question: So what does said exe does?
My Answer: I have no idea!
WAIT NONONONONO DON'T CLICK OFF FIRST! Uh well the exe is spread on discord so it likely steals your Discord Token, ROBLOSECURITY cookie, and credit card details to sell on some random black market for quite a huge sum of money, Yea most do that. Also it uses your discord account to send to your discord friends so DO NOT EVEN TOUCH IT, Unless you know what you're doing then uh your own risk not mine. Also you should maybe check links a bit more closely because for some reason www.example.com.[ INSERT NATIONAL DNS HERE ] is possible. Oh yea you could send an email to Red de Desarrollo Sostenible Honduras about www.roblox.com.hn and hopefully it gets taken down.

Oh yea I'm gonna scan the exe with https://www.virustotal.com/ and see what happensoh no I've lost access to the trojan because Windows 10's setup is litteraly the worst I've ever used so uh yea can't check sorry.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERYTHING TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 09:47:03 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>http://example.com</link>
      <author>johndoe@example.com</author>
      <comments>http://example.com</comments>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <enclosure url="BACKGROUND.BMP" length="308,278" type="image/bmp" />
      <description><![CDATA[This is to test absolutely everything I can do on this thing]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 08:19:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <description><![CDATA[TEST]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>