<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="rss.css" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>ORileyTan's Epic RSS Feed</title>
    <link>https://orileytan.github.io</link>
    <description>Where I post updates and other stuff that is not related to youtube such as update logs bla bla bla.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
              <item>
      <title>Oh no a friend got hacked!</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:23:28 +0700</pubDate>
      <category>Random Stuff</category>
      <description><![CDATA[Ok I still don't get how people still do click random exes on the internet. Oh yea the thing (From the spoof url) originates from Honduras so uh yea that's something. So the file I'm talking about is RobloxTool.exe which according to the very engrish added text file is "leaked method that Big game devs use to get big amounts of Robux or Items for free.", There is genuinely no way to get free robux unless it's a promotion or before 2016. Also Big Game's actual tool is Roblox Studio, They make games not handle the entire website and Roblox doesn't use exe files to test stuff they either use their site test sites or the ROBLOX account or some random alt not a random exe they don't even need it in the first place because of the important thing of they have direct access to site data...

Also instead of labling the attached txt file as "README.TXT" they just used "HowToDO.txt".

Possible Question: So what does said exe does?
My Answer: I have no idea!
WAIT NONONONONO DON'T CLICK OFF FIRST! Uh well the exe is spread on discord so it likely steals your Discord Token, ROBLOSECURITY cookie, and credit card details to sell on some random black market for quite a huge sum of money, Yea most do that. Also it uses your discord account to send to your discord friends so DO NOT EVEN TOUCH IT, Unless you know what you're doing then uh your own risk not mine. Also you should maybe check links a bit more closely because for some reason www.example.com.[ INSERT NATIONAL DNS HERE ] is possible. Oh yea you could send an email to Red de Desarrollo Sostenible Honduras about www.roblox.com.hn and hopefully it gets taken down.

Oh yea I'm gonna scan the exe with https://www.virustotal.com/ and see what happensoh no I've lost access to the trojan because Windows 10's setup is litteraly the worst I've ever used so uh yea can't check sorry.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERYTHING TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 09:47:03 +0700</pubDate>
      <link>http://example.com</link>
      <author>johndoe@example.com</author>
      <comments>http://example.com</comments>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <enclosure url="BACKGROUND.BMP" length="308,278" type="image/bmp" />
      <description><![CDATA[This is to test absolutely everything I can do on this thing]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 08:19:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <description><![CDATA[TEST]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
