<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="/asset/scripts/rssfeed.css" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>SUPER DUPER EPIC FEED THING THAT IS OUTDATED</title>
    <link>https://orileytan.github.io</link>
    <description>This thing is just a fun gimmick and test for web browsers to see if they still properly support RSS. Follow if you want to but the likelyhood of me posting here is very very small just follow me on twitter.

Built with RSS Builder by B!Soft</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Feel free to use this code. 2022</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>What I may add to this website?</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <category>Random Posts</category>
      <description><![CDATA[NO IDEA!..... well not really I have plans to add my personal website here and that's why I updated the site from the older file system to a newer one and rewrote all the webpages.
It's likely gonna be 90s style utilizing
<table cols=2 border=2>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>No.</td>
<td>Data.</td></tr>
<tr>
<td>1</td>
<td>TABLES!!!!!</td></tr>
<tr>
<td>2</td>
<td>
<p>WOW SO COOL!</p></td></tr>
<tr>
<td>3</td>
<td>PLEASE FOLOW MY TWITTER INSTEAD OF THIS!!!</td></tr></tbody></table>
And basically any 90s thing I can find such as websafe colors so very happy day for people who STILL USE A 256 COLOR DISPLAY DRIVER IN 2023!!! and it may or may not contain combustible lemons that burns your hose down.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Added a style for the RSS feed</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 9 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Building this site</category>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a tutorial online on how to do it and they let people use it, I'm gonna modify it although...]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other stuff</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <category>Random Posts</category>
      <description><![CDATA[As I've said I don't really post here just follow my twitter, It's listed on the main website unless you just wanted to do it anyways............................................ Oh yeah I may wipe stuff here due to storage but I don't know I guess if this thing reaches 1MB of occupied space or github doesn't like it at all]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTIFICATION TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://orileytan.github.io</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://orileytan.github.io</guid>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <description><![CDATA[I wanted to see how notifications work.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEST</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://orileytan.github.io</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://orileytan.github.io</guid>
      <category>TEST</category>
      <description><![CDATA[This is just to test feeds so there is nothing worthwhile here just follow my twitter instead]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
